hawaiis.com 2011-05-27

# American Dream Realty Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

  1. Our Commitment to Privacy. This notice describes our Privacy Policy. Our privacy policy is designed to advise you about how we collect, use, and protect the personal information you provide. By visiting this site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

  2. What Information is Collected.

(a) Information You Provide to Us: We may collect any information you enter on our site, or that you give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of our services and features.

(b) Automatic Information: When you visit a website, you disclose certain information, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time of your visit. This site, like many other sites, records this basic information about visits to our site.

(c) ``Cookies'': Cookies are pieces of information that are transferred to your computer from a web server. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or to refuse to accept cookies.

  3. How and When the Information is Used. The information we collect is used to send you new listings as they become available according to your preferences. You may opt out of these mailings at any time.

  4. How We Protect Your Information. The privacy and protection of your information is important to us. We do not make any personal information available to third parties without your permission, unless said information is the subject of a valid subpoena or other court order..

Your access to some services and content may be password protected. We advise that you do not disclose your password to anyone.

  5. Methods We Use to Protect Your Information. We use security software to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. In addition, our business practices are reviewed periodically for compliance with policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information. Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons.

  6. Children. This website does not provide services or sell products to children under the age of 18. [If you are under 18, you may use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.]

  7. Consent. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

  8. Changes to Privacy Policy. If our Privacy Policy or procedures change, we will immediately post those changes to our website. Any such changes will be effective immediately upon being posted, unless otherwise stated in the change.
